Guide to the New-York Historical Society Museum Department Records 1765, 1830-2018 NYHS-RG 20
New-York Historical Society
- Series III. Curatorial and Administration Files, 1934-2016; 50.87 Linear feet
  - Subseries III.A. General Files, 1934-1966, 1985-2001; 5.42 Linear feet
    - Set 1, 193x-196x (Box -, Folder -)
    - Museum/Registrar Files. A, 1939-1965 (Box 56, Folder 1)
      Includes, among others: Arkenburgh, Arnold, Andre, Agnew, Ainslie, American Museum of Natural History (loan of Catlin paintings for N-YHS's 1941 exhibition), auction receipts from Gimbel's.
    - Museum/Registrar Files. B (2 folders), 1939-1956 (Box 56, Folder 2-3)
      Includes, among others: Blake, Belknap, Bennet, Beekman, Berry, Oscar Barck (Field Exploration), Boardman, Barlow, Brainard.
    - Museum/Registrar Files. Blair, Mrs. J. Insley (2 folders), 1934-1942 (Box 56, Folder 4-5)
    - Museum/Registrar Files. C (2 folders), 1939-1949 (Box 56, Folder 6-7)
      Includes, among others: Cox, Connor, Cooper Union (loan for 1941 exhibition of textiles at N-YHS), Clement, Corell, Constant, Constantine.
    - Museum/Registrar Files. D, 1940-1960 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      Includes, among others: Dietrich, von Drehle, Dyer, Day.
    - Museum/Registrar Files. De Groot, Adelaide Milton, 1940-1947 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Museum/Registrar Files. E, 1939-1953 (Box 57, Folder 3)
      Includes, among others: Erwin, Van Horne Ellis.
    - Museum/Registrar Files. F, 1939-1958 (Box 57, Folder 4)
      Includes, among others: de Luze Foley, Stuyvesant Fish.
    - Museum/Registrar Files. G, 1939-1961 (Box 57, Folder 5)
      Includes, among others: Greenwood, Guernsey, Norvin Green, Richard Gosman estate, Gruver, Gilder.
    - Museum/Registrar Files. H (2 folders), 1939-1962 (Box 57, Folder 6-7)
      Includes, among others: Hand, Marian S. Hornor (loan of objects for N-YHS's 1942 St. Nicholas exhibition), Edgar C. Hyman Co., Havemeyer, Healy, Hirsch (loan of Benjamin West-related paintings by N-YHS to Allentown Art Museum), Hazen Hyde, Hudson River Line, Hanrick.
    - Museum/Registrar Files. I-J, 1939-1963 (Box 58, Folder 1)
      Includes, among others: Irwin, Jackson.
    - Museum/Registrar Files. L, 1939-1959 (Box 58, Folder 2)
      Includes, among others: Ellouise Baker Larsen, Landauer, Rita Lawrence.
    - Museum/Registrar Files. M-N (2 folders), 1939-1966 (Box 58, Folder 3-4)
      Includes, among others: Marwick, Macomber & Co. and other institutions/museums beginning with M (loan of textiles for N-YHS 1941 exhibition), Megrue, McKesson, Murphy, Newton, Catherine Mackie, Merritt, Abbie C. Miller, Mott.
    - Museum/Registrar Files. O-Q, 1939-1966 (Box 58, Folder 5)
      Includes, among others: Overton, Odell, Walter S. Poor, Prentis, F.E. Ogden (includes original photographs and descriptions of donated models of New York buildings), Beecher Ogden, O'Conor, Paltsits.
    - Museum/Registrar Files. R, 1939-1965 (Box 59, Folder 1)
      Includes, among others: Richards, Roudin, Root, Katherine Rogers, Francis Rogers, Rives.
    - Museum/Registrar Files. S-T (3 folders), 1939-1962 (Box 59, Folder 2-4)
      Includes, among others: Saint Nicholas Society, Turner, Taylor, Stahl & Sherwood (loan of objects for 1942 N-YHS New York Stage exhibition), list of silver stored in the vault at July 16, 1941, Ruth Ulmann Samuel, Sheean, Tomlinson Collection, Skillin, Schermerhorn, Sealy (Edward Wyer letterbook), Sherwood, Squier, Tinker, Tyler (Gallatin).
    - Museum/Registrar Files. U-V, 1939-1949 (Box 59, Folder 5)
      Includes, among others: Verplanck, Voorhies.
    - Museum/Registrar Files. W-Z (2 folders), 1939-1966 (Box 59, Folder 6-7)
      Includes, among others: Ziller, Zabriskie, Wheeler (Abeel kas, with original photograph), Garrett Winter, Louis C. Wills, Helen Wright, Wetherby, Whittemore.
    - Museum/Registrar Files. A, 1954-1957 (Box 60, Folder 1)
      Includes: Van Wyck Anthony, Douglas Anderson, Frederick B. Adams.
    - Museum/Registrar Files. B, 1948-1962 (Box 60, Folder 2)
      Includes, among others: Natalie K. Blair.
    - Museum/Registrar Files. Beekman, 1948-1958 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Museum/Registrar Files. Belmont, 1955-1962 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Museum/Registrar Files. C, 1935-1961 (Box 60, Folder 5)
      Includes, among others: Charles Halsey Clark, Carey, Chanler.
    - Museum/Registrar Files. D, 1950-1961 (Box 60, Folder 6)
      Includes, among others: Davis, Deavenport.
    - Museum/Registrar Files. Eberstadt, 1956 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Museum/Registrar Files. E-G, 1948-1962 (Box 60, Folder 8)
      Includes, among others: De Luze Foley, Ferguson, Stuyvesant Fish, Protestant Episcopal Church.
    - Museum/Registrar Files. Gallatin, 1951-1954 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Museum/Registrar Files. H-K, 1934-1964 (Box 60, Folder 10)
      Includes, among others: Horn, Harbord, Jay, James Foundation, Haacker, Herrick, Irwin, Keppler, Kimball.
    - Museum/Registrar Files. Hanks, 1959-1963 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Museum/Registrar Files. Hanna, 1950 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Museum/Registrar Files. Havemeyer (3 folders), 1949-1961 (Box 60, Folder 13-15)
    - Museum/Registrar Files. Kilroe, 1948-1950 (Box 60, Folder 16)
      Includes a booklet with original bookplates and descriptions, 1905-1944.
    - Museum/Registrar Files. K, 1939-1967 (Box 61, Folder 1)
      Includes, among others: Enit Kaufman, R. Keith Kane.
    - Museum/Registrar Files. L, 1939-1961 (Box 61, Folder 2)
      Includes, among others: Landauer, Linsley.
    - Museum/Registrar Files. Livingston, 1950-1960 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Museum/Registrar Files. Lockman, 1955-1958 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Museum/Registrar Files. M-P, 1948-1961 (Box 61, Folder 5)
      Includes, among others: McKim Mead & White, Paltsits, Hudson River Day Line (A.V.S. Olcott), McKay.
    - Museum/Registrar Files. Murdock, Undated (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Museum/Registrar Files. Murphy (Prentis), 1953-1957 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Museum/Registrar Files. Quistgaard, 1951-1965 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Museum/Registrar Files. R, 1954-1961 (Box 61, Folder 9)
      Includes, among others: Rockwell, Katherine R. Rogers, Rutledge.
    - Museum/Registrar Files. Ramage, 1947 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Museum/Registrar Files. Stuart, 1944 (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Museum/Registrar Files. Townsend, 1959 (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - Museum/Registrar Files. Vail, R.W.G., 1958-1960 (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Museum/Registrar Files. Varick Papers, 1960-1961 (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Museum/Registrar Files. Von Kienbusch, 1956-1960 (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - Museum/Registrar Files. V-Z, 1948-1960 (Box 61, Folder 16)
      Includes, among others: G. Creighton Webb, Davenport West, Westervelt, Welch, Zabriskie.
    - Correspondence re: possible future gifts and bequests, 1948-1980 (Box 61, Folder 17)
      Includes correspondence with James C. Daily (1948), Anna Marvin (1962), Nellie Kingsland (1967), and others.
    - Set 2 (Box -, Folder -)
    - Museum Correspondence (7 folders), 1992 June, 1993 February-1996 April (Offsite-box 62, Folder 1-7)
    - Museum Correspondence (5 folders), 1996 May-1997 June (Offsite-box 63, Folder 1-5)
    - Museum Correspondence (5 folders), 1997 July-1998 December (Offsite-box 64, Folder 1-5)
    - Museum Correspondence (5 folders), 1999 January-2000 May (Offsite-box 65, Folder 1-5)
    - Museum Correspondence (4 folders), 2000 July-2001 March (Offsite-box 66, Folder 1-4)
    - Museum Correspondence (4 folders), 2001 April-2002 May (Offsite-box 67, Folder 1-4)
    - Declined Offers (2 of 5 folders), 1995-2001 (Offsite-box 67, Folder 5-6)
    - Declined Offers (3 of 5 folders), 1985-2001 (Offsite-box 68, Folder 1-3)
  - Subseries III.B. Museum Collections Committee Files, 1977-2013; 10.13 Linear feet
    N-YHS restricts Board of Trustee and Executive Office files for 50 years following the departure of a President and Chief Executive Officer. This subseries includes files related to Board and Board Committee matters, and so is restricted accordingly. Records from 1977-1982 (from the administraton of James Heslin) are restricted until 2033. Records from 1983-1988 (from the administration of James B. Bell) are restricted until 2039. Files holding the records of Bell's successors will be opened in subsequent years. While the restriction applies, these records may be used only by, or with the permission of, the President and Chief Executive Officer, the head of the Museum Department, or their designee.
  - Subseries III.C. Mary Black Files, 1940, 1968-1983; 9.45 Linear feet
    The subseries includes files maintained by and for Mary Childs Black (referred to as "MCB" in many of the documents), who was Curator of Painting, Sculpture and the Decorative Arts at N-YHS from 1970 through 1982. Black was an authority on American folk art. Prior to joining N-YHS, she had been the Director of the Museum of American Folk Art in New York (1964-1970) and Director of the Abby Aldrich Rockefeller Collection at Williamsburg (late 1950s-1964).
    Black's records primarily include two overlapping sets of files, one ordered by subject and the other ordered chronologically. The chronological files generally hold only correspondence and the topics include proposed and executed exhibitions, publication and other projects, research inquiries, professional exchanges, offers of objects for accession, and other museum professional matters. The subject files also hold correspondence concerning the same general and even particular matters, but also hold a broader range of documentation, such as photographs, research notes on artists and other topics, drafts of articles and other writings, etc. The container list includes a complete list of the subject files, using the original label headings. These first two sets were processed and described in 2016; in 2021, additional materials from Black's files were transferred to the archves and these were described broadlt at the box level and are found at the end of the container list.
    It appears that many files related to specific exhibitions might have been removed from these records and boxed separately. For files of exhibitions during Black's tenure, at least many of which were surely from Black's office, see Series II. Exhibitions, Subseries A. General Files.
    Although the bulk of the material dates from the years of Black's tenure at N-YHS, there is a set of 1940s correspondence between the United States Trust Company of New York and the Museum of the City of New York concerning the bequest of a Trumbull portrait to MCNY, subsequently renounced in favor of N-YHS (see the Trumbull subject file).
    The subseries opens with the alphabetically arranged subject files followed by the chronological correspondence files. The subseries concludes with descriptions of content of boxes added to the finding aid in 2021.
    - A. General, 1976-1979 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 1)
    - Abby Aldrich Rockefeller, Williamsburg, 1978-1982 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 2)
    - Abigail Adams Smith Museum, 1981 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 3)
    - Abrams, Harry N., Inc., 1977 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 4)
    - Acknowledgements of Books, Catalogs, Etc., 1981 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 5)
    - Paintings, Furniture, Etc. in Storage, Paterson, NJ, 1969-1970 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 6)
    - Albany Institute of History & Art, 1976-1982 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 7)
    - Alland Collection (Bracklow Photographs), 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 8)
    - American Antiquarian Society, 1970s (Offsite-box 91, Folder 9)
    - American Art & Antiques, 1979 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 10)
    - American Craft Museum, 1981 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 11)
    - American Indian Relations, New York, 18th Century, Undated (Offsite-box 91, Folder 12)
    - American Society of Interior Decorators (Designers), 1980-1981 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 13)
    - American Society of Mechanical Engineers, 1978 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 14)
    - Amerika Haus Berlin, 1976-1977 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 15)
    - Amon Carter Museum of Western Art, 1972-1982 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 16)
    - Andrews, Faith (Mrs. Edward Deming), 1980-1981 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 17)
    - Annual Report, 1972-1975 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 18)
    - Antiques World, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 19)
    - Architectural Renderings, 1980 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 20)
    - Archives Reference & Research Advisory Board (New York City), 1981 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 21)
    - Aron, Bill (Photographer), 1978 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 22)
    - Art on the Road, 1980 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 23)
    - Art Commission (New York City), 1980-1981 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 24)
    - Art Institute of Chicago, 1981 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 25)
    - Associate Curator. Job Description, 1981 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 26)
    - Association of Historians of American Art, 1981 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 27)
    - Astoria Motion Picture & Television Foundation, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 28)
    - Audio-Visual & Films, 1975-1977 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 29)
    - B. General, 1971-1979 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 30)
    - Bank of New York, 1979 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 31)
    - Beard, Rick, 1980-1981 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 32)
    - Belmont (That Belmont Look), 1981 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 33)
    - Bailey, Rosalie Fellows, 1979-1981 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 34)
    - Bemis, William Otis. Biography, 1970s (Offsite-box 91, Folder 35)
    - Bicentennial, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 36)
    - Bicentennial Information Network (BINET), 1974 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 37)
    - Black, Mary Childs, 1974-1982 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 1)
      Includes miscellaneous memos, file inventory, a biographical sketch, and other documents.
    - Black Watch (Commander Force), 1979 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 2)
    - Blackburn, Roderic, 1974 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 3)
    - Boscobel Restoration, 1979 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 4)
    - Bradford Manuscript Exhibition, 1977 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 5)
    - Breaking Ground Exhibition, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 6)
    - Bridges, Charles, 1981 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 7)
    - Brighton Beach Project, 1976 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 8)
    - Brochures, 1973 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 9)
    - Brodsky. Gotham Medley, 1982 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 10)
    - Brooklyn Bridge, Modern Photographers Look At, 1981-1983 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 11)
    - Brown, O.J. (artist), 1977 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 12)
    - Bryan Collection. Sale (2 folders), 1978-1979 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 13-14)
    - Bundy, Horace, 1971 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 15)
    - Burton, Charles (artist), 1979 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 16)
    - C. General, 1971-1980 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 17)
    - Cabinetmaker (New York) and His Use of Space Exhibition, 1975-1976 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 18)
    - Calyo, Nicolino (artist), 1978-1981 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 19)
    - Caplan, Frank & Theresa (Creative Playthings) / Institute & Museum of Fantasy & Play, 1978-1982 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 20)
    - Carriage Collection, 1977 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 21)
    - Central Park, 1977 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 22)
      Includes offer by Hirschl & Adler Galleries of oil painting by Richards.
    - Chambers, Thomas (artist), 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 23)
    - Chambers, Winthrop (artist), 1980 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 24)
    - Channel 13, 1977-1980 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 25)
    - Childs Gallery, 1978-1982 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 26)
    - Christmas Museum Proposal, 1978 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 27)
    - Cole, Lyman Emerson, 1971 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 1)
    - Cole, Thomas (artist), 1979-1981 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 2)
    - Complaint Letters re: Exhibitions, 1981 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 3)
    - Computers & Word Processing. Museum, 1982 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 4)
    - Conservation, N-YHS, 1981 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 5)
    - Cooper-Hewitt Museum of Design, 1976-1977 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 6)
    - Crafft, R.B. (artist), 1971 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 7)
    - Crawford, Joyce, 1981 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 8)
    - Crawford, Thomas (artist), 1981 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 9)
    - D. General, 1976-1980 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 10)
    - Damages, Insurance, 1970 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 11)
    - Decker, Malcolm, 1975 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 12)
    - Delanoy (artist), 1980-1981 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 13)
    - Denby, Mrs. William, 1976-1977 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 14)
    - DePeyster Limner, 1971 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 15)
    - Dexter Hall, 1968-1973 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 16)
    - Dover Publications, 1971-1977 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 17)
    - Draper, Ruth (accession sheets), 1977 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 18)
    - Dunn, Malcolm (appraiser), 1982 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 19)
    - Durand, Asher B. (artist), 1976-1980 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 20)
    - Durand, John (artist), 1980-1981 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 21)
    - Duyckincks (4 folders), 1973-1981 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 22-25)
    - E. General, 1979 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 26)
    - Eagles, 1970s (Offsite-box 93, Folder 27)
    - Earle, Ralph (artist), 1977-1980 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 28)
    - Eastern Mass. Artist, 1982 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 29)
    - Edson, Almira, 1982 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 30)
    - Education, 1970-1973 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 31)
    - 1890 House, 1977 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 32)
    - English Folk Art, 1978 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 33)
    - Entrance Fees, 1980 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 34)
    - Erastus Salisbury Field Exhibition, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 35)
    - European Painting, 1972 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 36)
    - Evaluations from Museum Workshop Program's Exhibition Workshop, 1978 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 37)
    - Exhibition Files (schedules, plans, proposals, etc.) (8 folders), 1973-1982 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 1-8)
    - F. General, 1973-1979 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 9)
    - Farancz, Alan (Paintings Restorer), 1970s (Offsite-box 94, Folder 10)
    - Field, Erastus Salisbury, 1970-1978 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 11)
    - Film Project, Historic New York, Hudson River Film Co., 1980 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 12)
    - Fisher / Fitch, 1981 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 13)
    - Flint Institute of Arts, 1976 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 14)
    - Folk Art (3 folders), 1971-1982 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 15-17)
    - Foote, Mary (artist), 1973-1974 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 18)
    - Francis, Undated (Offsite-box 94, Folder 19)
    - Freake Limner, Undated (Offsite-box 94, Folder 20)
    - Freenan, George (artist), 1981 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 21)
    - Frost, J.O.J (artist), 1971 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 22)
    - Frymire, Jacob (artist), 1982 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 23)
    - G. General, 1972-1979 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 1)
    - Gallery Association of New York State, 1977-1980 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 2)
    - Gallery at the Old Post Office, 1982 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 3)
      Concerns Manhattan Observed and Breaking Ground exhibitions.
    - Gershinowitz, George, 1982 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 4)
    - Gifford, Sanford Robinson, 1981 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 5)
    - Gift/Donation Refusals, 1980-1981 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 6)
    - Gill, Jill (2 folders), 1975-1981 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 7-8)
    - Glass Files, 1976-1977 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 9)
    - Goelet List, Undated (Offsite-box 95, Folder 10)
    - Gracie Mansion (3 folders), 1982 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 11-13)
      Includes Black's edited typescript for her "Gracie Mansion: A History of the Mayor's House" and related matter.
    - Gracie Mansion (4 folders), circa 1977-1981 (Offsite-box 313)
      Includes, among other documents, blueprints of the preliminary plans for Gracie Mansion prepared by William C. Shopsin
    - Greeley & Forest Forgeries. Research, Undated (Offsite-box 95, Folder 14)
    - Greenleaf, Benjamin (artist), 1981 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 15)
    - Greitzer, Carol (councilwoman), 1981 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 16)
    - Guy, Francis, 1981 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 17)
    - H. General, 1971-1979 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 18)
    - Hartwell / Haspel (artists), Undated (Offsite-box 95, Folder 19)
    - Heaton, John, 1972-1980 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 20)
    - Herot, George (artist), 1975 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 21)
    - Herring, James (artist), 1975 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 22)
    - Hicks, Edward, 1970-1980 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 23)
    - Hirschl & Adler Galleries, 1979-1982 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 24)
    - Hoelzer, Hiram (restorer), 1974 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 1)
    - Holsapple / Hopkins / Hovey, 1981 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 2)
    - Holt, Henry, 1978-1982 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 3)
    - Horton, Carolyn (restorer), 1978 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 4)
    - Hudson Valley Dutch Museum Survey, 1982 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 5)
    - Hudson Valley Studies, 1977 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 6)
    - Huntington, Daniel, 1970 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 7)
    - Hyde de Neuville, Baroness, 1972-1977 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 8)
    - I. General, 1976-1979 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 9)
    - Iconography, 1979 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 10)
    - Importance of Being Hyphenated, 1981 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 11)
    - Insley, Albert, 1982 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 12)
    - Interior Design Fair New York City, 1979 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 13)
    - Internal Revenue Service, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 14)
    - International Celebration of Art, 1981 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 15)
    - International Center for Photography, 1978 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 16)
    - International Exhibitions Foundation, 1982 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 17)
    - Interoffice Memos, 1976-1977 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 18)
    - Inventories. N-YHS Manuscript Collection, Undated (Offsite-box 96, Folder 19)
    - J. General, 1980-1981 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 20)
    - Jarvis, John Wesley, 1981 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 21)
    - John Judkin Memorial, 1978-1981 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 22)
    - Justus Dalee, 1974 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 23)
    - K. General, 1973-1978 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 24)
    - K and L. General, 1978-1979 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 25)
    - L. General, 1979-1983 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 26)
    - Kaplan Fund (2 folders), 1979-1982 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 27-28)
    - Kern, Arthur, 1979-1982 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 29)
    - Kilburn, Lawrence, 1981 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 30)
    - Kindig, Paul E. / Pennsylvania Butter Prints, 1982 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 31)
    - Kingston, NY, History of, 1974 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 32)
    - Knickerbocker Birthday, 1979 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 33)
    - Landscape Catalog, 1971-1982 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 34-35)
    - Lesueur, 1974 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 36)
    - Lewis, Jerry (Federal Hall Chairs), 1982 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 37)
    - Lighting Fixtures. Case, 3rd Floor West Corridor, Undated (Offsite-box 96, Folder 38)
    - Limners of the Upper Hudson, 1968-1978 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 39)
    - Love Galleries, 1982 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 1)
    - Lynes, Russell, 1981 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 2)
    - Lyons, Louis and Paul Hollister (Glass), 1977 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 3)
    - M. General, 1978-1979 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 4)
    - Maentel, Jacob (2 folders), 1971-1980 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 5-6)
    - Magriel, Paul, 1980 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 7)
    - Manhattan Now (Manhattan Observed), 1981 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 8)
    - Marling, Jacob, 1977 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 9)
    - Minnigerode, Marietta (artist), 1980 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 10)
    - Movers (Global), 1977 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 11)
    - Moynihan, Daniel Patrick, 1981 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 12)
    - MTA Bus Ex. / Dover Book, 1982 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 13)
    - MTA. N-YHS Station, 1979 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 14)
    - Munson-Williams-Proctor Institute, 1978-1982 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 15)
    - Museum of American Folk Art, 1971-1972 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 16)
    - Museum of the City of New York, 1979 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 17)
    - N. General, 1976-1980 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 18)
    - National Gallery of Art, 1979-1982 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 19)